-Any
Speaker 1: questions, please? -Mr.
Speaker 2: President, in addition to this big announcement, you've also been posting about Iran today, opposing their latest demands. You said this last round of talks was Iran's last chance before decapitation. So what now? What
Speaker 3: comes next? -You'll find
Speaker 2: out. -Are you still -- a massive escalation, is that still on the table?
Speaker 3: -Well, we have that certainly -- that ability, if we want to do that. Yeah, you'll find out.
Speaker 2: -You said you're low-keying it
Speaker 2: Are they semi-negotiating? What exactly does that mean? Well,
Speaker 3: they asked for reparations, you might say, or they asked for money for the damage that we've done. I said, that's a good idea. Well, we're going to ask for money for the damage they've done over a 50 year period, whether you go SS coal or whether you go all of the people that were so badly hurt, so badly wounded or killed, many thousands of people.
And
Speaker 3: maybe damages for the 52,000 protesters over the last four months that were killed in Iran. We think their family should get damages for killing their person or their child or mother, father that we're protesting. At least it was 52,000 a month and a half ago. So now what is it? So if there's damages to be paid, I think Iran should pay those damages.